A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, First Administration, Series 37.1 FA439
Rockefeller Archive Center
- First Administration, 1959-1962; 1; 171 microform reels
  - Fiscal (Reel 30, Reel 31, Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35, Reel 36)
    - Expenditures (Reel 31, Reel 32)
      - General (Reel 32)
        - New York City - New York State Relationship (Reel 32)
        - State Aid (Reel 32)
        - General (Reel 32)
    - Revenue (Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35, Reel 36)
      - Tax & Finance (Reel 32)
        - Income Tax Bureau (Reel 32)
        - Budget (Reel 32)
          - 1959-1962 (Reel 32)
          - General (Reel 32)
        - General (Reel 32)
      - Motor Vehicle. Department
        - Accident Forms (Reel 32)
        - Department of Compulsory Auto Inspection (Reel 32)
        - Compulsory Auto Insurance (Reel 33)
        - Operator's License (Reel 33)
        - Special License Plates (Reel 33)
        - License Plates (Reel 33)
        - Statistical Reports (Reel 33)
        - Uniform Traffic Tickets (Reel 33)
        - General (Reel 33)
      - Taxation
        - Cigarette & Tobacco Income (Reel 33)
        - Federal Tracking Industry (Reel 33)
        - Gasoline Tax (Reel 34)
        - Governor's program (Reel 34)
        - Non-Resident Income Tax (Reel 34)
          - Connecticut (Reel 34)
          - New Jersey (Reel 34)
          - General (Reel 34)
        - Income Tax Rebate (Reel 34)
        - Income Tax (Reel 34)
        - Income Tax (Reel 35)
        - Lottery and Legalized Gambling (Reel 35)
        - New Jersey Emergency Transportation Tax (Reel 35)
        - New York City Sales Tax (Reel 35)
        - Off-Track Betting (Reel 35)
        - Property Tax (Reel 35)
          - Foreign Government (Reel 35)
          - Borough of Richmond (Reel 35)
          - General
            - 1961-1962 (Reel 35)
            - 1959-1960 (Reel 36)
        - State Sales Tax (Reel 36)
        - Telephone Service (for school use) (Reel 36)
        - Tolls (Reel 36)
        - Track Mileage & Weight Distance Tax (Reel 36)
        - Unincorporated Business Trip (Reel 36)
  - Fund Raising (Reel 36)
    - Albany Community Chest (Reel 36)
    - American Cancer Society (Reel 36)
    - Cerebral Palsy (Reel 36)
    - Heart Fund (Reel 36)
    - Jewish Welfare Fund (Reel 36)
    - March of Dimes (Reel 36)
    - Mental Health Appeal (Reel 36)
    - Muscular Dystrophy (Reel 36)
    - Red Cross (Reel 36)
    - Salvation Army (Reel 36)
    - United Fund (Reel 36)
    - Variety Club Camp Thatcher (Reel 36)
    - General (Reel 36)
  - Government (Reel 36, Reel 37, Reel 38, Reel 39, Reel 40, Reel 41, Reel 42, Reel 43, Reel 44, Reel 45)
    - Federal (Reel 36, Reel 37)
      - Aviation Authority (Reel 36)
      - Communications Commission (Reel 36)
      - Department of Health, Education & Welfare (Reel 36)
      - Housing & Home Finance Agency (Reel 36)
      - Immigration & Naturalization (Reel 36)
      - Inauguration (Reel 37)
      - Department of Interior (Reel 37)
      - Department of Labor (Reel 37)
      - Post Office (Reel 37)
      - United States Atomic Energy Commission (Reel 37)
      - General (Reel 37)
    - International (Reel 37, Reel 38)
      - Africa (Reel 37)
      - Argentina (Reel 37)
      - Australia (Reel 37)
      - Austria (Reel 37)
      - Belgium (Reel 37)
      - Bolivia (Reel 37)
      - Brazil (Reel 37)
      - Canada (Reel 37)
      - Chile (Reel 37)
      - China (Reel 37)
      - Colombia (Reel 37)
      - Cuba (Reel 37)
      - Denmark (Reel 37)
      - El Salvador (Reel 37)
      - Ethiopia (Reel 37)
      - France (Reel 37)
      - Germany (Reel 37)
      - Ghana Great (Reel 37)
      - Britain (Reel 37)
      - Greece (Reel 37)
      - Guatemala (Reel 37)
      - Guinea (Reel 37)
      - Haiti (Reel 37)
      - Indonesia (Reel 37)
      - Iran (Reel 37)
      - Ireland (Reel 37)
      - Israel (Reel 37)
      - Italy (Reel 37)
      - Japan (Reel 37)
      - Jordan (Reel 37)
      - Korea (Reel 37)
      - Latin America (Reel 37)
      - Liberia (Reel 37)
      - Mexico (Reel 37)
      - Morocco (Reel 37)
      - Nepal (Reel 37)
      - Netherlands (Reel 37)
      - Nicaragua (Reel 38)
      - Nigeria (Reel 38)
      - Norway (Reel 38)
      - Pakistan (Reel 38)
      - Panama (Reel 38)
      - Peru (Reel 38)
      - Philippines (Reel 38)
      - Portugal (Reel 38)
      - Puerto Rico (Reel 38)
      - Red China (Reel 38)
      - South Africa (Reel 38)
      - South America (Reel 38)
      - Spain (Reel 38)
      - Sudan (Reel 38)
      - Thailand (Reel 38)
      - Tunisia (Reel 38)
      - USSR (Reel 38)
      - Uruguay (Reel 38)
      - Venezuela (Reel 38)
      - Others (Reel 38)
    - General (Reel 38)
      - Foreign Policy (Reel 38)
      - Summit Conference (Reel 38)
      - International Official Visitor's Bureau (Reel 38)
      - United Nations (Reel 38)
    - State (Reel 39, Reel 40)
      - Alaska (Reel 39)
      - Arizona (Reel 39)
      - California (Reel 39)
      - Colorado (Reel 39)
      - Connecticut (Reel 39)
      - Florida (Reel 39)
      - Hawaii (Reel 39)
      - Idaho (Reel 39)
      - Illinois (Reel 39)
      - Indiana (Reel 39)
      - Iowa (Reel 39)
      - Louisiana (Reel 39)
      - Maryland (Reel 39)
      - Massachusetts (Reel 39)
      - Michigan (Reel 39)
      - Minnesota (Reel 39)
      - Montana New (Reel 39)
      - Hampshire (Reel 39)
      - New Jersey (Reel 39)
      - North Carolina (Reel 39)
      - North Dakota (Reel 39)
      - Ohio (Reel 39)
      - Pennsylvania (Reel 39)
      - Rhode Island (Reel 39)
      - Tennessee (Reel 39)
      - Texas (Reel 39)
      - Utah (Reel 39)
      - Vermont (Reel 39)
      - Virginia (Reel 39)
      - Washington (Reel 39)
      - West Virginia (Reel 39)
      - Wisconsin (Reel 39)
      - Others
        - A-M (Reel 39)
        - N-Z (Reel 40)
      - Compacts Agreement or Retainers (Reel 40)
        - Conserve Gas (Reel 40)
        - Juveniles (Reel 40)
        - Mental Health (Reel 40)
        - New York & New Jersey Transportation (Reel 40)
        - Supervision of Parolees & Probationers (Reel 40)
      - General (Reel 40)
    - City (Reel 40, Reel 41)
      - Albany (Reel 40)
        - South Mall (Reel 40)
        - General (Reel 40)
      - Amsterdam (Reel 40)
      - Batavia (Reel 40)
      - Binghamton (Reel 40)
      - Buffalo (Reel 40)
      - Elmira (Reel 40)
      - Hornell (Reel 40)
      - Hudson (Reel 40)
      - Ithaca (Reel 40)
      - Jamestown (Reel 40)
      - Lockport (Reel 40)
      - New York City (Reel 40)
        - City Council (Reel 40)
        - New York City Police Department (Reel 40)
        - General (Reel 40)
      - Newburgh (Reel 40)
      - Niagara Falls (Reel 40)
      - Ogdensburg (Reel 40)
      - Olean (Reel 40)
      - Oswego (Reel 40)
      - Rochester (Reel 40)
      - Rye (Reel 41)
      - Schenectady (Reel 41)
      - Syracuse (Reel 41)
      - Utica (Reel 41)
      - Yonkers (Reel 41)
      - Others (Reel 41)
    - County (Reel 41, Reel 42, Reel 43)
      - Albany (Reel 41)
      - Alleghany (Reel 41)
      - Bronx (Reel 41)
      - Broome (Reel 41)
      - Cattaraugus (Reel 41)
      - Cayuga (Reel 41)
      - Chataugua (Reel 41)
      - Chenango (Reel 41)
      - Columbia (Reel 41)
      - Cortland (Reel 41)
      - Delaware (Reel 41)
      - Dutchess (Reel 41)
      - Erie (Reel 41)
      - Franklin (Reel 41)
      - Genesee (Reel 41)
      - Greene (Reel 41)
      - Hamilton (Reel 41)
      - Kings
        - 1960-1962 (Reel 41)
        - 1959 (Reel 42)
      - Monroe (Reel 42)
      - Montgomery (Reel 42)
      - Nassau (Reel 42)
      - New York (Reel 42)
      - Niagara (Reel 42)
      - Oneida (Reel 42)
      - Onondaga (Reel 42)
      - Orange (Reel 42)
      - Orleans (Reel 42)
      - Oswego (Reel 42)
      - Putnam (Reel 42)
      - Queens (Reel 42)
      - Rensseleaer (Reel 42)
      - Rockland (Reel 42)
      - St. Lawrence (Reel 42)
      - Saratoga (Reel 42)
      - Schenectady (Reel 42)
      - Schoharie (Reel 42)
      - Suffolk
        - 1960-1962 (Reel 42)
        - 1959 (Reel 43)
      - Sullivan (Reel 43)
      - Tioga (Reel 43)
      - Ulster (Reel 43)
      - Warren (Reel 43)
      - Wayne (Reel 43)
      - Westchester (Reel 43)
      - Yates (Reel 43)
      - Others (Reel 43)
    - Town (Reel 43)
      - Hancock (Reel 43)
      - Harrison (Reel 43)
      - Hampstead (Reel 43)
      - Lindenhurst (Reel 43)
      - Rockville Center (Reel 43)
      - Valley Stream (Reel 43)
      - West Seneca (Reel 43)
      - Others (Reel 43)
    - Local (Reel 43, Reel 44)
      - Office for Local Governor (Reel 43)
        - Equalization & Assessment Board (Reel 43)
        - Fire Training & Mobilization (Reel 43)
        - Municipal Police Training (Reel 44)
        - General (Reel 44)
      - General (Reel 44)
        - Home Rule (Reel 44)
        - General (Reel 44)
    - General (Reel 44, Reel 45)
      - Certificates of Good Citizenship for Voting (Reel 44)
      - New Citizens
        - 1961-1962 (Reel 44)
        - 1959-1960 (Reel 45)
      - General (Reel 45)
  - Health & Sanitation (Reel 45, Reel 46, Reel 47)
    - Hospitals (Reel 45)
      - J. W. Adams Memorial Hospital (Reel 45)
      - Albany (Reel 45)
      - Bellevue Hospital (Reel 45)
      - Brooklyn Hebrew Home and Hospital for the Aged (Reel 45)
      - Children Asthma Research Institute (Reel 45)
      - City of Hope National Medical Center (Reel 45)
      - Deborah Hospitals (Reel 45)
      - Hospital for Special Surgery (Reel 45)
      - Jewish Chronic Disease Hospital (Reel 45)
      - Kings County Hospital (Reel 45)
      - Mount Morris Park Hospital (Reel 45)
      - National Jewish Hospital (Denver) (Reel 45)
      - Rehabilitation Hospital (West Haverstraw) (Reel 45)
      - Roosevelt Hospital (Reel 45)
      - Roswell Park Memorial Institute (Reel 45)
      - Saint Oinens Hospital (Reel 45)
      - Veterans Administration Hospital (Reel 45)
      - Others (Reel 45)
      - General (Reel 45)
    - Health (Reel 45, Reel 46)
      - Department of (Reel 45)
        - Foreign Medical Students (Reel 45)
        - Inspection (Reel 45)
        - Publications (Reel 45)
        - General (Reel 45)
      - Topics (Reel 46)
        - Air Pollution (Reel 46)
        - Alcoholism (Reel 46)
        - Birth Control (Reel 46)
        - Cancer (Reel 46)
        - Cystic Fibrosis (Reel 46)
        - Employment of Osteopaths in Hospitals (Reel 46)
        - Food & Drugs (Reel 46)
        - Heart Disease (Reel 46)
        - Incinerators (Reel 46)
        - Influenza (Reel 46)
        - Narcotic Council on Drug Addiction (Reel 46)
        - Narcotics (Reel 46)
        - Polio (Reel 46)
        - Radiation (Reel 46)
        - Water Fluoridation (Reel 46)
        - Water Pollution (Reel 46)
          - Blatnick Bill (Reel 46)
          - Sewage (Reel 46)
          - General (Reel 46)
        - Water Supply (Reel 46)
        - Others (Reel 46)
    - General (Reel 47)
      - Interdepartmental Health & Hospital Council (Reel 47)
      - State Hospital Review & Planning Council (Reel 47)
      - General (Reel 47)
  - Honorary Designation (Reel 47, Reel 48)
    - 1960 May-1961 (Reel 47)
    - 1959-1960 April (Reel 48)
  - Horse Racing (Reel 48, Reel 49)
    - Flat (Reel 48)
      - Canandaigua (Reel 48)
      - State Racing Commission (Reel 48)
      - General (Reel 48)
    - Harness (Reel 48)
      - Racing Commission (Reel 48)
        - Investigation (Reel 48)
        - General (Reel 48)
    - General (Reel 49)
      - General (Reel 49)
      - Minors at Tracks (Reel 49)
  - Housing (Reel 49, Reel 50, Reel 51, Reel 52, Reel 53, Reel 54)
    - Division of (Reel 49)
      - Bureau of State Building Code (Reel 49)
      - General (Reel 49)
    - Construction & Repairs (Reel 49)
      - Finances (Reel 49)
        - Mortgages Facilities Corporation (Reel 49)
        - Limited Profit Housing Mortgage Corporation (Reel 49)
        - General (Reel 49)
      - Interior Windowless Rooms (Reel 49)
      - Urban Renewal Localities (Reel 49)
      - Planning (Reel 49)
      - Title I (Reel 49)
      - General (Reel 49)
    - Low & Middle Income (Reel 49)
    - Housing Projects (Reel 50, Reel 51, Reel 52, Reel 53)
      - Rochdale Village (Reel 50)
      - Lakeside Village (Reel 50)
      - Woodlawn Veterans Cooperative (Reel 50)
      - Queensburo Hills (Reel 50)
      - Others (Reel 50)
      - General (Reel 50)
      - Rent Commission (Reel 50)
      - Rent Control
        - 1961 March-1962 (Reel 50)
        - 1960 June-1961 January (Reel 51)
        - 1960 February-May (Reel 52)
      - Clinton Hill Apartments (Reel 52)
      - Copies of Letters from Rent Commission (Reel 52)
      - Rent Control (Reel 53)
        - 1959 (Reel 53)
    - Tenant Problems (Reel 53)
      - Accommodations (Reel 53)
        - Low & Middle Income (Reel 53)
        - Projects (Reel 53)
        - Relocation (Reel 53)
        - General (Reel 53)
      - Eviction (Reel 53)
      - Lease (Reel 53)
        - Security Deposits (Reel 53)
        - General (Reel 53)
      - Maintenance & Repairs (Reel 53)
      - General (Reel 53)
    - General (Reel 54)
      - Landlord Problems (Reel 54)
      - General (Reel 54)
  - Insurance (Reel 54, Reel 55, Reel 56)
    - Department of (Reel 54)
    - General (Reel 54, Reel 55, Reel 56)
      - Accidents (Reel 54)
        - State Employment in Aircraft (Reel 54)
        - General (Reel 54)
      - Auto Liability (Reel 54)
      - Health
        - Aging
          - 1961 July-December (Reel 54)
          - 1960 January-1961 June (Reel 55)
        - Catastrophic Study (Reel 55)
        - Health Rates (Reel 55)
        - State Employment (Reel 55)
        - General
          - 1962 (Reel 55)
          - 1959-1961 (Reel 56)
      - Life Insurance (Reel 56)
        - State Employees (Reel 56)
        - General (Reel 56)
      - General (Reel 56)
  - Investigations (Reel 56, Reel 57)
    - Commission on (Reel 56)
      - Albany County (Reel 56)
      - Bingo (Reel 56)
      - Buffalo (Reel 56)
      - Cabaret Licenses (Reel 56)
      - Hulan, Jack (Reel 56)
      - City of Ithaca (Reel 56)
      - Nassau County (Reel 56)
      - New York City (Reel 56)
      - Oneida County (Reel 56)
      - Suffolk County (Reel 56)
      - City of Utica (Reel 56)
      - Ulster County (Reel 56)
    - General (Reel 57)
  - Invitations (Reel 57, Reel 58, Reel 59, Reel 60)
    - 1962 (Reel 57)
    - 1960 October-1961 December (Reel 58)
    - 1959 August-1960 April (Reel 59)
    - 1959 February-June (Reel 60)
  - Judiciary (Reel 60, Reel 61)
    - Courts (Reel 60, Reel 61)
      - Court of Appeals (Reel 60)
      - Court of Claims (Reel 60)
      - County Courts (Reel 60)
      - Federal Courts (Reel 61)
      - New York City Courts (Reel 61)
      - Supreme Court (Reel 61)
        - Extraordinary & Special Trial Term (Reel 61)
        - General (Reel 61)
      - General Court Reform (Reel 61)
      - Increase in Judges (Reel 61)
      - Judicial Conference (Reel 61)
      - Jury Duty (Reel 61)
      - Litigation (Reel 61)
      - General (Reel 61)
  - Labor (Reel 61, Reel 62, Reel 63, Reel 64, Reel 65, Reel 66, Reel 67, Reel 68, Reel 69)
    - Department of (Reel 61, Reel 62)
      - Interdepartmental Committee on Low Income (Reel 61)
      - Advisory Council on Labor Management Improper Practice (Reel 61)
      - Labor Relations Board (Reel 61)
      - Division of Manpower (Reel 62)
      - Migratory Labor Camp Conditions (Reel 62)
      - T.V. Program "Harvest of Shame" (Reel 62)
        - Virginia Incident (Reel 62)
        - General (Reel 62)
      - State Board of Standards & Appeals (Reel 62)
      - State Insurance Fund (Reel 62)
      - General (Reel 62)
    - Benefits (Reel 62, Reel 63)
      - Unemployment Insurance (Reel 62)
        - 1961 July-1962 (Reel 62)
        - 1959-1961 June (Reel 63)
      - Workmen's Compensation (Reel 63)
        - 1961-1962 (Reel 63)
        - 1959-1960 (Reel 64)
    - General (Reel 64)
    - Mediation & Arbitration (Reel 64)
      - Letters & Commendation (Reel 64)
      - General (Reel 64)
    - Minimum Wages (Reel 64)
    - Social Security (Reel 64, Reel 65)
      - 1962 (Reel 64)
      - 1959-1961 (Reel 65)
    - Strikes (Reel 65, Reel 66)
      - Carier Corporation (Reel 65)
      - General Electric Company (Reel 65)
      - Gideon Putnam Hotel (Reel 65)
      - Harbor Tugboat Men (Reel 65)
      - Horse Racing (Reel 65)
      - Hospitals (Reel 65)
      - Jamestown-Sterling Corporation (Reel 65)
      - Metropolitan Opera (Reel 65)
      - Milk (Reel 65)
      - Newspaper (Reel 65)
      - New York City Transit & Subway (Reel 66)
      - Radio Station (WNDT) (Reel 66)
      - Railroads (Reel 66)
        - Long Island Railroad (Reel 66)
        - General (Reel 66)
      - Steel (Reel 66)
      - Teachers (Reel 66)
      - Waterfront Longshoremen (Reel 66)
      - General (Reel 66)
    - Unemployment (Reel 66, Reel 67, Reel 68)
      - Senate Hearing at Schenectady (Reel 66)
      - Localities by County (Reel 66)
      - General (Reel 66)
      - Employment
        - Division of
          - Council on Employment & Unemployment Insurance (Reel 66)
          - Employment Service (Reel 67)
        - Latin American Office (Reel 67)
        - Physically Handicapped (Reel 67)
        - Committee on Employment of the Handicapped (Reel 67)
        - Youth Employment Service (Reel 67)
        - General (Reel 67)
        - Unemployment Insurance
          - 1959 July-1962 (Reel 67)
          - 1959 January-June (Reel 68)
        - General (Reel 68)
    - Workmen's Compensation Board (Reel 68)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 68)
      - General (Reel 68)
      - Moreland Act Commission (Reel 68)
    - Workmen's Compensation (Reel 68)
      - Review Committee (Reel 68)
      - General (Reel 68)
    - General (Reel 68, Reel 69)
      - Automation Acknowledgement (Reel 68)
      - Article: "Automation Here to Stay" (Reel 68)
      - Invitation for Conference (Reel 68)
      - Regret for Conference (Reel 68)
      - Thank You Letters (Reel 68)
      - Automation
        - Governor's Conferences on Automation (Reel 68)
      - General
        - 1962 (Reel 68)
        - 1959-1961 (Reel 69)
      - Employment Agencies (Reel 69)
      - Governor's Council on Rehabilitation (Reel 69)
      - Labor Relations Act (Reel 69)
        - Employees of Non-Profit Agencies (Reel 69)
        - Vesting of Pensions (Reel 69)
        - Wage Claims (Reel 69)
      - General (Reel 69)
  - Law (Reel 69, Reel 70)
    - Department of (Reel 69)
      - Complaints & Proceedings (Reel 69)
      - Counsel Meetings (Reel 69)
      - General (Reel 69)
    - General (Reel 69, Reel 70)
      - Alcoholic Beverage Control Laws (Reel 69)
      - Constitutional Amendments (Reel 69)
      - Daylight Saving Time (Reel 69)
      - Domestic Relations (Divorce) (Reel 69)
      - Election Law Frauds (Reel 69)
      - Qualifications
        - 18-year-old vote (Reel 69)
        - Suffrage Article (Reel 69)
        - Reapportionment (Reel 70)
        - Registration (Reel 70)
        - Time off to vote (Reel 70)
      - Election Law (Reel 70)
      - Holidays (Reel 70)
        - Good Friday (Reel 70)
        - Three-day Weekend (Reel 70)
        - Others (Reel 70)
      - Obscene Literature (Reel 70)
      - Opinions Public Prayers in Schools (Reel 70)
      - Sabbath Law (Reel 70)
      - Marie Torre Case (Reel 70)
      - Opinions (Reel 70)
      - General (Reel 70)
  - Legislation (Reel 71, Reel 72, Reel 73, Reel 74, Reel 75, Reel 76, Reel 77, Reel 78, Reel 79)
    - 1962 (Reel 71, Reel 72)
      - Federal (Reel 71)
      - State
        - Administration (Reel 71)
        - Aging (Reel 71)
        - Agriculture (Reel 71)
        - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 71)
        - Banking (Reel 71)
        - Civil Defense (Reel 71)
        - Commerce (Reel 71)
        - Conservation (Reel 71)
        - Discrimination (Reel 71)
        - Education (Reel 71)
        - Fiscal (Reel 71)
        - Government (Reel 71)
        - Health (Reel 71)
        - Housing (Reel 71)
        - Insurance (Reel 71)
        - Judiciary (Reel 71)
        - Labor (Reel 71)
        - Law (Reel 71)
        - Licensing Chiropractors (Reel 71)
        - Licensing (Reel 71)
        - Mental Hygiene (Reel 71)
        - Military & Naval (Reel 71)
        - Personnel Administration (Reel 71)
        - Property (Reel 71)
        - Public Safety (Reel 71)
        - Public Utilities (Reel 71)
        - Public Works (Reel 71)
        - Social Welfare (Reel 71)
        - Veterans (Reel 71)
        - Youth (Reel 71)
        - General (Reel 72)
    - 1961 (Reel 72, Reel 73, Reel 74)
      - Federal (Reel 72)
        - Foreign Aid (Reel 72)
        - General (Reel 72)
      - State
        - Agriculture (Reel 72)
        - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 72)
        - Banking (Reel 72)
        - Bill Signing (Reel 72)
        - Civil Defense (Reel 73)
        - Commerce (Reel 73)
        - Conservation (Reel 73)
        - Correction (Reel 73)
        - Discrimination (Reel 73)
        - Education (Reel 73)
        - Fiscal (Reel 73)
        - Government (Reel 73)
        - Health (Reel 73)
        - Housing (Reel 73)
        - Insurance (Reel 73)
        - Judiciary (Reel 73)
        - Labor (Reel 73)
        - Law (Reel 73)
        - Licensing (Reel 73)
        - Mental Hygiene (Reel 73)
        - Military & Naval (Reel 73)
        - Personnel Administration (Reel 73)
        - Property (Reel 73)
        - Public Safety (Reel 73)
        - Public Utilities (Reel 73)
        - Public Works (Reel 73)
        - Welfare (Reel 73)
        - Youth (Reel 73)
      - General
        - Legislative Proposals (Reel 73)
        - Special Sessions (Reel 74)
        - General (Reel 74)
    - 1960 (Reel 74, Reel 75)
      - Federal (Reel 74)
      - State
        - Agriculture (Reel 74)
          - Milk Dating (Reel 74)
          - General (Reel 74)
        - Banking (Reel 74)
        - Civil Defense (Reel 74)
        - Conservation (Reel 74)
        - Discrimination (Reel 74)
        - Education
          - Carnegie Hall (Reel 74)
          - School Bus Transportation (Reel 74)
          - New York City Teachers Retirement System (Reel 75)
          - General (Reel 75)
        - Fiscal (Reel 75)
        - Government (Reel 75)
        - Health (Reel 75)
        - Horse Racing (Reel 75)
        - Housing (Reel 75)
        - Insurance (Reel 75)
        - Judiciary (Reel 75)
        - Labor (Reel 75)
        - Law (Reel 75)
        - Licensing (Reel 75)
        - Military & Naval (Reel 75)
        - Pen Certificates (Reel 75)
        - Personnel Administration (Reel 75)
        - Property (Reel 75)
        - Public Safety (Reel 75)
        - Public Utilities (Reel 75)
        - Public Works (Reel 75)
        - Reorganization (Reel 75)
        - Welfare (Reel 75)
        - Youth (Reel 75)
        - General (Reel 75)
    - 1959 (Reel 76, Reel 77, Reel 78)
      - Federal (Reel 76)
      - State
        - Aging (Reel 76)
        - Agriculture (Reel 76)
        - Banks (Reel 76)
        - Civil Defense (Reel 76)
        - Commerce (Reel 76)
        - Conservation (Reel 76)
        - Disaster (Reel 76)
        - Discrimination (Reel 76)
        - Fiscal (Reel 76)
        - Health & Sanitation (Reel 76)
          - Nuclear Research Center (Reel 76)
          - General (Reel 76)
        - Horse Racing (Reel 76)
        - Housing (Reel 76)
        - Housing (Reel 77)
        - Insurance (Reel 77)
        - Investigation (Reel 77)
        - Judiciary (Reel 77)
        - Labor (Reel 77)
        - Licensing (Reel 77)
        - Mental Hygiene (Reel 77)
        - Military & Naval (Reel 77)
        - Parks & Recreation Facilities (Reel 77)
        - Pen Certificates (Reel 77)
        - Personnel Administration (Reel 77)
        - Property (Reel 77)